是穆奇来收租了
Okay, that's Mookie for the rent money.
我刚在沙发里找出两张5块
I just found two fives in the couch!
也就是5块 10块 进位...
Which brings us to 5, 10, carry the one...
进到了人生新低
a new low.
你们好 我叫默里
Hello, I'm Murray.
是你们点了火速达印度菜吗
Did you order Curry In A Hurry?
不确定啊 付过钱了吗
I don't know. Is it paid for?
付过了
Yeah.
那没错 是我们点的
Then, yes, we did.
麦克斯 你太坏了
Max, you're awful.
我们才没有付钱
We didn't pay for that.
这是印度菜
It's Indian food.
三小时后我们就会去厕所"付"出代价
We'll pay for it in three hours.
里面有咖喱角吗
Any samosas in there?
要来点烤饼吗
You want some naan?
点这餐的人只能骂哇"烤"了
'Cause whoever ordered it ain't gettin' naan.
有看到火速达印度菜的默里吗
Did you guys see Murray with our Curry In A Hurry?
没 抱歉
Nope, sorry.
提醒你们一声 咖喱角做得有点干
Just a heads up, the samosas are a little dry
而且全被吃完了
and also completely gone.
我需要补充大量精力
I need all the energy I can get.
我跟苏菲无时无刻都在床上大战
Sophie and I are doin' it 'round the clock.
她超级想怀上孩子
She wants a baby so bad,
手机上还下了一个排卵提醒软件
she even got an ovulation app on her phone.
苏菲的手机还有生育软件啦
Sophie's phone has a fertility app?
我的手机老到都生不出屁了
My phone's so old it can't get pregnant.
告诉我们她什么时候最可能怀孕
Tells us when she's most fertile.
其实呢 是一只卡通小猴子提醒我们
Actually, a little cartoon monkey tells us.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
过度好奇的乔治吗
Overly curious George?
奥列格 吉时已到 你看
Oleg, it's time. See?
这猴子都一柱擎天了
The monkey's got a boner.
我挺确定那根东西是香蕉
I'm pretty sure that's a banana.
那根东西又黄 它手又握着 绝对是肉棒
It's yellow and he's holding it. It's a boner.
苏菲 期望别太高
Sophie, don't get your hopes up.
我们大战过三万回合
We've had so much sex,
现在基本上射出来的都是蒸汽了
it's basically just steam coming out now.
你找到外卖啦 太好了
Oh, you found the food. Good.
你不介意我用你的肚子当托盘
You mind if I use your stomach as a tray
你边"做" 我边吃吧
so I can eat while we do it?
我有介意过吗
Do I ever mind?
我每天得无视超多事情 才得以度日
I have to block out so much now just to get through the day.
我们这里客似云来
Wow, we have more visitors than
比动漫大会上平凡货色妓女的恩客还多
a mildly attractive prostitute at Comic-Con.
是穆奇来收租了
It's Mookie for the rent.
麦克斯 这一次可以由你来
Okay, Max, this time can you do
跟他做那个击拳爆炸的招数吗
the blow-it-up hand thing with him?
我试过了 但我"手上功夫"就是不好
I've tried it, but I'm just not good at hand stuff.
问当年耶鲁大学的同志们就知道
Ask anyone at Yale PREP.
你就试试嘛
Just give it a shot!
你也曾经觉得自己吃不了被踩过的食物
You also thought you couldn't eat food that's been stepped on.
你看你现在多行
Look at you now.
女士们好啊 抱歉我迟到了
Sup, ladies? Sorry I'm late.
有人朝我扔了一只猫
Some guy threw a cat at me.
今天谁来跟我击拳爆炸啊
Who's gonna blow it up for me?
我被禁止再让任何东西爆炸了
I'm not allowed to blow stuff up anymore.
我假释官定的规矩 不是我
My parole officer's rules, not mine.
我知道击得很烂 对不起
I know that was bad. I'm sorry.
有没有学习班可以报名啊
Is there a class I can take?
我去拿最后那一部分房租
I'll go get the last of the rent money.
要么是在我胸罩堆里 不然就是没有
It's either in my bra pile, or I don't have it.
你慢慢找 没事
Take your time. We cool.
所以"穆奇"这名字是怎么来的
So, what kind of name is "Mookie"?
是什么东西的简称吗
Is it short for something?
还是什么东西的长版叫法吗
Long for something?
麦克斯 赶紧找
Max, hurry up, girl.
你手上应该有800块
Okay, you should have $800
这里是剩下的尾款
and here's the last of it.
好嘞 我得走了
Sweet. Well, I gotta go.
我还有网球课
I got a tennis lesson.
卡洛琳 想再试一次吗
Caroline, wanna try again?
确定好825块都捡齐了
Make sure you get the whole $825.
小太妹别想偷偷抽回两张
No funny business down there, gangsta.
825块 租金不是850块吗
825? The rent is 850.
没有啊 一直都是825块
No, always been 825.
现在说啥呢
What's going on now?
麦克斯 你为啥骗我房租是850块
Max, why do you tell me the rent's 850 if it's 825?
好的 我先撤了
Oh, yeah, I'ma go ahead and--
祝你好运
good luck with that.
你一直以来都多收我房租吗
You've been overcharging me rent?
不是这样的
It's not like that.
怎么个不是这样
How is it not like that?
好啦 的确是这样
Okay, it's exactly like that.
说认真的 麦克斯 除了房租这事
Seriously, Max, other than the rent,
你还有什么事没跟我说实话
what else have you not been telling the truth about?
你估计也没有在超市遇见明星吧
You probably didn't even see Emma Stone at Costco.
还有 麦克斯·布莱克是你的真名吗
And is Max Black even your real name?
这是一个真的名字
It's a real name.
为我自己辩解一下
Hey, in my defense,
你的卧室的确比较大啊
you do have a bigger bedroom.
那是因为我睡在客厅
That's because I sleep in the living room.
你不能就让这件事翻篇吗
Can you just let this go?
我就多抽了点油水而已嘛
So I took a little off the top.
大家都会抽点油水啊
Everybody takes a little off the top.
你看上帝抽走阿憨多少
Look what God did to Han.
别把我拖进你们俩的《美少女的谎言》里
Don't drag me into the middle of Pretty Little Liars.
我家里养的两只貂在闹肠胃炎
I've got two ferrets at home with the stomach flu,
我才懒得陪你们扯皮
and I don't need it.
请所有员工停下手边没在干的工作
Now everyone stop what you're not doing.
我要开紧急员工会议
I'm calling an emergency staff meeting.
不会又是要说
Is this the whole,
"不许在食物槽里冰敷鸡巴"的这件事了吧
"Don't ice your junk in the food sink" thing again?
不是 我有一个规矩
No, I have a rule.
警告达20次后 我就放弃那件事
20 warnings, then it's a dead issue.
这会议是跟你们所有人有关
This is about all of you.
我们需要谈谈餐厅的团队合作
We need to talk about diner teamwork.
我们团队合作很好
Oh, our teamwork's fine.
比如我们现在就帮厄尔打掩护
For example, we're covering for Earl
好让他能出去买冰激凌吃
while he chases the ice cream man.
买到巧克力夹心雪糕啦
Got me a Chaco Taco.
大家统统坐下
Everybody, sit down.
为啥 所以能跟我们平视吗
Why? So we can be eye level?
这句羞辱得好 卡洛琳
Good put-down, Caroline.
你看 阿憨 团队合作
See, Han? Teamwork.
好 来听听我们最新的点评网点评
All right, listen to our latest Yelp reviews.
达利尔B留言
Daryl B. Says,
"在卡座里坐了一个小时才有人搭理我
"Sat in booth an hour before anyone talked to me.
而搭理我的原因
When someone did,
居然是服务员要我给她倒水"
it was the waitress asking me for water."
我当时很口渴嘛
I was thirsty!
而这个达利尔B当时端水速度慢死了
And Daryl B. Was real slow with that water.
我也没上点评网唧唧歪歪啊
You don't see me Yelping about it.
我也来念一个
I'll read one.
来自这里的卡洛琳C留言
Caroline C. from here says,
"在过去四年里 麦克斯每月多收我25块房租"
"Max has been overcharging me $25 a month for four years."
听起来就像乱编的
That sounds made up.
明天晚上 本餐厅休息一晚
So tomorrow night, I'm closing the diner,
我们大家去做团队建设活动
and we're all working on our team building skills.
没人在意
So no one cares that
麦克斯每个月偷我25块钱吗
Max has been stealing $25 a month from me?
没错
That's correct.
这边请
Right this way.
这里是什么鬼
What the hell is this place?
这里看起来像我小时候
This looks like the room I was kept in
被陌生司机叔叔借走三天时 住的地方
when that trucker borrowed me for three days.
你也有多收他借用费吗
Did you overcharge him too?
我们很快就会知道这里是哪里啦
You'll all find out where we are soon enough.
这也是冒险的一部分
All part of the adventure,
还是神秘... 还有...
and the mystery, and the--
我说过冒险了吗
did I say adventure?
惨了 这里不会是那种密室逃脱
Oh no, this isn't one of those escape rooms
就是把你们关在一个房间里
where they lock you in a room
得齐心协力合作才能逃出的地方吧
and you have to work as a team to get out?
欢迎来到密室逃脱
Welcome to the Escape Room,
就是把你们关在一个房间里
where we lock you in a room,
得齐心协力合作才能逃出的地方
and you have to work as a team to get out.
好戏上场啦
And so it begins!
哪出好戏 我们暴打你的这出吗
What? Us beating the crap out of you?
当然啦 是男女混合双"打"
Together, of course.
让我问清楚
Now let me get this straight.
你们都自愿
Y'all are volunteering
被锁进一个小房间里吗
to be locked up in a tiny room?
这真是死白人才会玩的玩意
See now, that's some white people stuff right there.
这是一种比较娱乐的方式
It's a fun way for us all to learn
来让我们学会如何合作解决问题
how to work together to solve a problem.
如果我们这群人能合作解决问题
If the group of us could work together to solve a problem,
你早被我们弄回韩国了
you'd be back in Korea.
我完全不着急回去找苏菲
I'm in no rush to get home to Sophie.
虽然我爱她这个狐媚子
I mean, I love her and she's a fox,
但造人过程太辛苦了
but baby-making is brutal.
我受够我双脚整天得举在空中了
I'm so tired of having my legs up in the air.
你怎么... 你都...
How do you-- What do you--
为什么是... 我们还是跳过这话题吧
How would that-- Let's just move past it.
请签这个弃权声明
Sign these waivers saying that
就是如果出了任何意外
if anything happens to you,
完全是你们自己的责任
it is entirely your fault.
大家别签这个 我们又不是白痴
Nobody's signing these waivers. We're not idiots.
我们得逐条读上面的合同细则
We're gonna read through all the fine print.
-好了 -给
- Done. - Here you go.
好吧 但我要先好好读过才签
Oh, well, I'm gonna read mine anyway.
卡洛琳什么都读
Caroline reads everything.
她甚至把苹果无数页的用户协议读完了
She read the entire iTunes user agreement before she bought
就因为要买蕾哈娜那首《贱人快还我钱》
Rihanna's "Bitch Better Have My Money."
真希望我在当你室友前
Wish I'd read the fine print
有先读过合同细则
when I agreed to be your roommate.
我才发现原来"贱人真欠了我钱"
Turns out, bitch do have my money.
我也得逃离这个吗
Do I have to escape from this too?
这也是游戏的一部分吗
I mean, is this part of the game?
我如果现在告诉你
Is this a bad time to tell you
是你的马策划的这一切 是不是时机不对
your horse masterminded the whole thing?
在开始前 我得先收走你们手机
Before we start, I need to collect your phones
以防你们上网找答案
so you can't Google answers.
别看我的屏保图片
Don't look at my screensaver
除非你特别不怕恶心
unless you have a strong stomach.
小弟我也算阅图无数
I've seen lots of phones.
想吓到我是得...
It takes a lot to shock-- Aah!
为什么你的脚在举空中
Why are your legs up?
亮起白灯就表示可以进了
Ah, white light means it's a go.
稍等
Hey, hold up! Aah!
等我一下
Oh, one second.
我喘气喘得比
You know, I'm breathin' harder
老年女星上《与星共舞》还厉害
than Paula Deen on Dancing with the Stars.
苏菲
Sophie?
你是怎么知道我在这里
How did you find me here?
我早告诉过你
I told you to take that
把"找出我老公"的软件卸载了
"Find My Husband" App off your phone.
我没卸载
Yeah, well... I didn't.
我们正在努力造人中
Yeah. We're trying to make a baby.
苏菲 你现在不能在这里
Sophie, you can't be here right now.
这是我工作的团队建设活动
This is a work team-building thing
你不是我工作团队中的一员
and you're not part of the team.
-对吧 阿憨 -她可以留下啊
- Right, Han? - She can stay.
她对餐厅的贡献跟她俩一样 都是零
She does as much at the diner as the girls do.
我不能离奥列格太远
Well, I gotta stay close to Oleg.
那只小猴无法预料
You know, the monkey's unpredictable.
你不知道它什么时候会要求性交
You never know when he's gonna demand intercourse.
有趣有趣
Well, that's a fun wrinkle.
这是我这辈子见过最死白人的事了
Okay, this is the whitest thing I've ever seen,
而我可是见过五趾鞋的人呢
and I've seen those shoes that have toes.
我了个去
Oh, hell no.
我感觉到了生气 害怕
I'm feeling angry, scared,
与麦克斯的一对巨乳
and both of Max's boobs.
那这算是我们版本的"和好炮"吗
Is this our version of make-up sex?
我什么都看不到
I can't see a thing!
来 用我的防狼胡椒喷雾手电筒
Here, let me use my pepper spray flashlight.
我开始喜欢上这活动了
Hey, I'm starting to like this now.
快看那些怪怪的灯开关
Hey! Look at all those kooky light switches!
快来试试
Let's try that!
不管这个人是谁 他说
Whoever this guy is says,
"选错的话要倒扣五分钟哦"
"Choose correctly or lost five minutes."
奥列格 不管"那个人"是谁 你绝对比不上
Wow, you're no whoever that guy is, Oleg.
10个 20个 26个开关
10, 20, 26 switches!
还有什么东西是26个
What other things are 26?
26 正好比麦克斯从我这偷走的钱多1块
Hmm, that's one more dollar than Max has been stealing from me.
不如举个更普遍一点
How about something a little more universal
少烦人很多点的例子
and a lot less annoying?
字母表里有26个字母
There are 26 letters in the alphabet.
谢谢 袋鼠同志们
Thank you, Comrade Kangaroo.
26个字母里 哪个可以代表光
Okay, 26 letters. Which one could represent light?
光的英文首字母是"L"
Light starts with "L"!
哇 他真厉害
Oh, wow, he's good!
太简单了 这人是爱因斯坦
Too easy. It's Einstein
答案一定跟科学有关
so the answer must be scientific.
等等 爱因斯坦最著名的等式E=mc2
Wait, in Einstein's famous formula E=mc2,
光的速度是用字母"C"来表示
the speed of light is represented by the letter "C."
A B C
A...b...c.
是爱丽丝梦游仙境主题
Oh, it's Alice in Wonderland themed!
这个我在行
I'll be great at this.
我以前最爱这个故事了
It was always my favorite story.
我和苏菲只看过"真枪实弹"的黄片版本
Sophie and I only watch the hard-core porno version.
对啊 那部片叫《爱丽丝淫游内境》
Yeah, it was called Alice in Underpants.
而且我们的牙医也有参演哦
And our dentist was in it!
你们的闲聊该结束了
That's enough of all your chatter!
是时候听疯帽子说两句了
It's time to listen to the Mad Hatter.
我觉得是之前那个人扮的
I think it's the same guy as before.
他真是个天才
He's a genius!
你们用光照亮了这间房子
You filled this room with illumination,
但你们现在走不出这房子
but you are not done with this situation.
跟"踢爆你蛋蛋"押韵的句子是什么
What rhymes with "Kick in the crotch"?
继续解谜 早点完事
To proceed and be done with me,
你们必须解出这三个谜语
you must answer these riddles three.
你们都知道我80岁了吧
Y'all know I'm 80, right?
一 从包装拿出
One: Take it out of the package.
塞进嘴巴里
It goes in your mouth.
越嚼越久越没味
Chew it too long, and it will go south.
厄尔就在干这事啊
It's what Earl's doing right now.
天啊 我尿出来了吗
Oh, Lord, am I peeing?
没啦 他在嚼口香糖
No, he's chewing gum.
"从包装拿出 塞进嘴巴里
"Take it out of the package. It goes in your mouth.
越嚼越久越没味"
Chew it too long and it'll go south."
就是口香糖啊
Gum.
相当正确[西语]
Exactamente.
看吧 也没这么难
That wasn't too hard.
把你的答案放到这张卡片上
Put your answer onto this card.
干得好
Well done!
这张团购券已经回本了
This Groupon has already paid for itself.
二 阿诺德·斯瓦辛格的"这个"很长
Two: Arnold Schwarzenegger's is big;
迈克尔·J·福克斯[演员]的"这个"短
Michael J. Fox's is small;
罗马教皇从不用自己的"这个"
the Pope has one but doesn't use it;
而麦当娜根本没有"这个"
Madonna doesn't have one at all.
鸡巴 答案是鸡巴
Dongs. The answer is dongs.
拜托 奥列格 没人敢确定
C'mon, Oleg, I mean nobody can say for sure
麦当娜到底有没有那玩意
that Madonna doesn't have one.
鸡巴不是一切问题的答案
Dongs aren't the answer to everything.
我曾这么认为
I used to think that.
你们知道那使我走向何处吗
You know where that got me?
宾夕法尼亚州 还没车
Pennsylvania, with no car.
斯瓦辛格的长 福克斯的短
Schwarzenegger's big, Fox's small.
是姓氏 教皇不用自己姓氏
It's last names. The Pope doesn't use his.
"麦当娜"这艺名里 根本没有姓氏
Madonna doesn't have one at all. That's it!
太对了[西语]
Correctamundo.
你的脑子这么聪明
With your brain power,
不到一个小时肯定能出去
you'll be out of here in under an hour.
谢谢 但如果我真的这么聪明
Well, thanks, but if I was that smart,
就不会在过去四年里
I wouldn't have spent the last four years
被我室友当傻子坑了
getting ripped off by my roommate.
拜托 你还在计较那钱的事吗
Oh, come on, are you still on the money?
我姐在收割机意外中 失去两根大拇指
Oh, my God, my sister lost both her thumbs in a combine accident
她也没你这么叫苦连天
and she didn't talk about it this much.
给 这里是25块
Ah, here's $25.
姑且就将其称为"封口费"
Let's call it hush money,
封上你的嘴吧
so hush.
首先 这里只有12块
First of all, this is $12,
而且好吧
and fine,
我的嘴再也不会说半句话
you won't hear a peep out of me anymore.
随便 出不出去我又无所谓
Fine, I don't care if we never get out.
好了 告诉大家一下
All right, FYI,
我和奥列格要把这里变成色情场所喽
yeah, Oleg and I are gonna get really Amsterdam-y up in here.
好吧 我们得马上出去
All right, we gotta get the hell out.
拜托 卡洛琳 你的奇思妙想呢
Come on, Caroline. Where's your sense of whimsy?
别说被麦克斯偷走了
And don't say Max stole it,
因为你的牢骚比兰迪的假口音还让人腻味
because that's getting older than Randy's accent.
抱歉 兰迪 我知道你人好不介意被吐槽
Sorry, Randy, I knew you were a safe person to slam.
时光一去不复返
Time moves forward. It doesn't go back.
你们还剩15分钟 已经过了45分钟了
You've got 15 minutes. It's 45 that you lack.
加油 伙计们
Come on, guys.
我们不需要卡洛琳帮我们解谜
We don't need Caroline to solve these puzzles.
我们之前也协心协力
This is the same team that was able
破解过餐厅隔壁
to figure out the Wi-Fi password
那间女子收容所的无线密码
to the women's shelter next to the diner.
这是谁说的
Who said this?
"如果之前是 那可能是
"If it was so, it might be;
如果之前可能 那将会是"
and if it were so, it would be."
这对肥胖双胞胎吗
The fat twins?
因为那句子根本不通
'Cause that made no sense
而他们看起来像是嗨高说胡话的样子
and they look like they get stoned a lot.
好了 奥列格 把裤子脱了
Okay, Oleg, drop your pants.
猴子要吃香蕉啦
The monkey wants his banana.
卡洛琳
Caroline,
如果我要看着奥列格 像捏喇叭那样捏她奶子
if I have to see Oleg so much as honk one of her boobs,
我会疯掉的
I'm gonna lose it.
我很想帮你 当你的天使
I would help you, and be your heaven-sent,
但你在房租上骗了我
but you screwed me on the rent.
到底要怎么做这事才能翻篇
What is it gonna take to make you get over this?
你甚至都还没跟我道歉
You haven't even apologized.
好吧 对不起
Okay. I am sorry.
我们没事了吧
Are we good?
不 我们可有事了
You know what? No, we not good.
不是吧
Aw, come on!
好吧 我是唯一一个知道这个故事的人
Fine, I'm the only one here who knows this story,
我也是唯一一个知道怎么出去的人
and I'm the only one who knows how to get out of here.
在那 那个兔子洞
There, the rabbit hole,
爱丽丝跳了进去 我也会
Alice went down and so will I.
真是够了
That's it.
这事简直比麦克斯的未来还惨不忍睹
This is a bigger bust than Max's future.
就像爱丽丝 我受够了被困在
Just like Alice, I'm sick of being stuck
这个是非颠倒的世界了
in this upside-down world
你的死党居然会骗你房租钱
when your best friend lies about the rent.
-你不能跳 -我当然能
- No, you can't! - Oh, yes, I can.
各位告别了[西语]
I bid you adieu.
不 说真的 别跳
No, seriously, don't!
我要跟着跳
Ooh, I'm next!
我不是故意要打击你们
I don't mean to burst your bubble,
但你们的朋友现在有难
but your friend's in a lot of trouble.
我想说的是
What I'm saying is:
那不是房间的一部分 只是摆摆样子而已
that's not part of the room. That's just for show.
你们不该跳进去
You're not supposed to jump in it.
我不跳了
I'm not next.
所以那不是一个可爱的兔子洞吗
So that's not a cute rabbit hole?
兔子 没有
Rabbits? No.
耗子倒有几只
Couple of rats, though.
这地方真的好危险
This place is a deathtrap.
卡洛琳 拜托告诉我你没事
Caroline, please tell me you're okay.
不行 因为我有事
I can't, because I'm not.
我会用紧急密码放我们出去
I'll use the emergency code to get us out of here.
好吧 我现在真的要对你们说实话
Okay, I'm gonna be real honest with you right now.
我不知道密码是啥
I don't know the codes.
救命 下面有东西在动
Help, there's something moving down here!
我要进去
I'm going in.
苏菲 把你的胡椒喷雾手电给我
Sophie, give me the pepper spray flashlight.
好的
All right, yeah.
快点
Hurry!
那玩意真的好刺
That really does sting.
奥列格 吉时已到
Okay, Oleg, now it's time.
那美好的一刻又到了
It's that beautiful moment
我们又要造人了
where you and I are gonna make a baby
还是当着你工作伙伴的面
right in front of your coworkers.
我们就不能有点档次
Can we have a little more class
等上了计程车再干吗
and wait till we get in the cab?
什么
What?
我们要在童话小茶杯上开干
We're gonna do it on top of teacups.
那可是相当上档次啊
That's pretty classy.
这是什么情况
What is happening?
知道吗
You know what?
把那玩意喷一些到你脑子里吧
Spray some of that stuff in your mind.
麦克斯 看
Max, look.
怪不得他要把腿抬到空中
Oh, that's why his leg's up in the air.
我看够了 我要走了
I've seen enough. I'm out.
我好像踩到会动的东西了
Ugh, I think I landed on what was moving.
所以那玩意死翘翘了
So that's dead now.
天啊 你没事吧
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
没事 你呢
Yeah, I think. Are you?
没事
Yeah.
等等 你刚不是说有事吗
Wait, you said you weren't okay.
我是指情绪上啊
I meant emotionally.
我居然为了你的情绪跳地板洞
I jumped into a floor hole for feelings?
我的情绪可是相当受伤啊 麦克斯
Well, my feelings are really hurt, Max.
整整四年呢
It's been four years.
我不知道该怎么做
Well, I don't know what to do,
因为就像疯帽子说
because like the Sad Hatter said,
时光一去不复返
time goes forward; it doesn't go back.
我不能抹掉房租的事
I can't undo the rent thing.
我只是以为我们是同甘共苦
I just thought we were in this together,
是啊
We are,
我四年前就该告诉你
and I should have told you four years ago,
但我当时觉得我们长不过一个月
but I thought we wouldn't last a month.
但后来一个月过去了 又一个月过去了
But then we did, and then another month,
我现在也还不知道怎么发生的
and I'm still not sure how this happened:
我们就成为死党了
we became best friends.
麦克斯 这是第一次不用讨好你
Max, that's the first time you've ever called me
你自愿称我为死党
your best friend without a bribe,
那比钱有价值多了
and that's worth a lot more than money,
你也知道我有多爱钱是吧
and you know how much I love money.
是啊 你差点为了钱毁了我们的友情
Yeah, you almost ruined our friendship over it.
好了 来吧 咱们赶紧离开这
All right, come on, let's get out of here.
我有事
I'm not okay.
脚剧痛 脚剧痛
Searing pain, searing pain.
我可能跳下来的时候扭到脚踝了
Ugh, I think I twisted my ankle when I jumped down here.
天啊 真对不起
Oh, my God. I am so sorry.
你说得对
You're right.
有时候道歉完全没用
Sometimes sorry just doesn't cut it.
那我们要怎么把你弄出去呢
So how are we gonna get you out of here?
如果你想让我背你
If you want me to carry you,
麻烦先把你的巨乳卸掉
you'll have to take off your boobs.
我们应该走哪边
Which way should we go?
我的烂方向感导致我在布鲁克林当服务员
My sense of direction led me to being a waitress in Brooklyn.
要不就往前走吧
You know what? Let's go forward.
就像时间一样 只能往前不能回头
'Cause much like the time, you can't go back.
而且那会动的玩意苏醒了 看起来很生气
Also, the moving thing just came to and looks mad.
走吧
Go.
麦克斯 我从未跟你的屁股如此靠近
Max, I've never been this close to your butt before,
你屁股真壮观啊
and it's spectacular!
你的秘密是什么
What's your secret?
我今年27岁
I'm 27.
我真的不该看到这画面
I really shouldn't be seeing this.
我们能把灯关掉吗
Can we please turn the lights back off?
老天 救我
Oh, God, help me!
在下面有个好处就是
Well, one good thing about being down here:
苏菲和奥列格在上面
Sophie and Oleg are up there.
等等 地板怎么在晃
Wait, why is the floor sagging?
老天
Oh, my God.
我很确定这一摔
You know, I'm pretty sure that fall
能把宝宝送进我的子宫里
knocked the baby right up into me.
更正一下 如果我能让时光倒流
Correction, if I could turn the clock back,
我不会回到四年前
I wouldn't go back four years.
我要回到30秒前
I'd go back 30 seconds.